clickbooth.com 2018-07-02

# Privacy Policy : Clickbooth Support

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Clickbooth.com, LLC (referred to herein as “We”, “Us,” or Clickbooth”) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the [www.clickbooth.com](http://www.clickbooth.com/) website (“Website”). This Privacy Policy applies to the website and all mobile applications, products and services offered by Clickbooth.com (collectively, the “Site”).  By visiting or using the Site, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Users of the Site include consumers who visit the Site and affiliates and advertisers who work with Clickbooth via the Site and provide us with personal information.

 **INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We may collect personal information from users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.

 **PERSONAL INFORMATION  **

Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities and our being able to provide certain services to users and to interact with users, such as in an affiliate or advertiser relationship with us.  For visitors to the Site who do not share any information with us, we collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of such visitors to our Site.  

 **AFFILIATES AND ADVERTISERS**

We may collect personal information when you (i) register on the Site, (ii) fill out forms or fields on the Site, (iii) complete an application for a product or service available through the Site; and (iv) communicate with us by email, mail, text, telephone, facsimile or other electronic means. Personal information in this context may include: your name, email address, and your credit card number.  Please note that we store only truncated credit card information.

We may also collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about users’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system, the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information, your mobile device type, your device’s unique identifier and your mobile network information.

 **OTHER USERS**

For other users of the Site (non-affiliates and non-advertisers), we collect information such as IP addresses and information regarding your browser name, the type of computer and technical information about users’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system, the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information, your mobile device type, your device’s unique identifier and your mobile network information.

We collect personal information if you provide information such as your name, e-mail or telephone number in the context of making an inquiry through our Site.

 **WEB BROWSER COOKIES**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance user’s experience.  We use cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our Site, record past activity at a Site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our Site, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

User’s web browsers place cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. A user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do refuse cookies, please note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

 **THIRD PARTY INFORMATION COLLECTION/”DO NOT TRACK”**

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Site. As a result of your visit to our Site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of the companies representing the ads or <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on the Site or to display advertising based upon your web browsing or application activity use Flash cookies and HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. To manage Flash cookies, please click here:  <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

“Do-Not-Track” is an optional browser setting that allows you to express your preferences regarding tracking by advertisers and other third-parties. We do not currently respond to Do-Not-Track signals.

If you wish to limit the collection of information by us or third party partners to provide you with advertising based upon your website browsing activities and interests, you may click [[http://preferences-mgr.truste.com](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/)] to opt out. To opt out of targeted advertising on your mobile device, iOS users can click here:  <https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT205223> to learn how to limit ad tracking and Android users can click here: <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en> to learn how to opt out of interest-based ads. Please note that opting out of interest-based/targeted advertising does not limit all advertising. You will continue to receive generic advertisements.

 **HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Site, used to customize the content and/or layout of our Site for each individual visitor, used to notify users about updates to our Site and marketing offers, and, shared with other organizations to help them contact consumers for marketing purposes.  More specifically, we may also use your information:

 _\- To serve your requests and offer our services_

 _\- To improve customer service_

Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests, fulfill your requests, and support needs more efficiently.

 _\- To personalize user experience_

We may use information individually or in the aggregate to understand how our users individually or as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

 _\- To improve our Site_

We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

 _\- To send periodic emails, mailings, and contact you telephonically_

We may use your contact information to respond to your inquiries, questions, and/or other requests and to send you promotions or other offers that may be of interest to you

 _\- To protect against certain activities_

We may use your information to protect our Site, our partners and affiliates, you, other users, and the public against potentially prohibited or illegal activities, including fraud.

 _\- To fulfill legal requirements_

We may use your information to fulfill applicable legal requirements, such as responding to subpoenas seeking user information

 _\- To provide targeted marketing and advertising.  _

We may use your information to send you marketing and advertising from us and our partners and affiliates that we think may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive such marketing and advertising, please see our instructions below or follow the opt-out instructions in the marketing or advertising you receive.

 _\- To conduct research_

We may use your information to conduct research and analysis for a variety of purposes, including to better understand our customers, to assist with our current and future service offerings, and to understand our website visitors better.

 _\- To manage and protect our information technology infrastructure and security_

We may use your information to help manage, secure and protect our IT infrastructure and to protect the security of our Site.

 _\- For any other purpose with your consent_

We may share with third parties the information we collect regarding IP addresses and information regarding browser name, the type of computer and technical information about users’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system, the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information, your mobile device type, your device’s unique identifier and your mobile network information.

We may use your information for any other purposes with your consent.

 **OPTING-OUT**

If you supply us with your e-mail address, you may receive periodic e-mails from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not want to receive e-mails from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail to: support@clickbooth.com.  However, we may still contact you concerning administrative or transactional matters.

If you supply us with your postal address, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided below, writing to us at the below address, or e-mailing us at support@clickbooth.com.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by calling us at the number provided below, writing to us at the below address, or e-mailing us at support@clickbooth.com.

 **HOW WE SHARE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers or any other party for any purposes including the purposes outlined above. In addition, we may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. In addition, we may share personal information:

\- To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of Clickbooth’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which information held by Clickbooth is among the assets transferred;

\- To fulfill any purpose or effect the action for which you provide the information;

\- To any third party with your consent;

\- To comply with any court order, law, legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request;

\- To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements, including for collections purposes and disbursements; or

\- If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Clickbooth, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other organizations for the purposes of fraud protection.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to information that we have collected and that we maintain about them.  

 **HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION**

We adopt reasonable data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.  In the context of a transfer of credit card information (such as for processing), that information is encrypted.  Also, we store only a truncated portion of credit card information.  

You should note that the security of your personal information also depends on you.  Please do not communicate any information to us through unsecured channels, such as when you are in public areas. Where we have provided you or you have chosen a password, access code, or similar security feature, you must keep the password, access code or security feature confidential. Please do not share your password with anyone. If you believe your password or account has been compromised, please contact us immediately at support@clickbooth.com.

Please note that the transmission of information via the Internet or other means of communication is not completely secure.  Although we take reasonable measure to secure your information, we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted to our Site or through other means of communication.  Any transmission of information is at your own risk.  We are not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy setting or security measures contained on any of our systems, including but not limited to our Site.

 **ACCESSING AND CORRECTING YOUR INFORMATION**

You may send us an email at support@clickbooth.com to correct or delete any information that you have provided to us.  We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect or misleading.

 **CHILDREN UNDER 13**

Our Site and products or services available through this Site are not intended for children under 13 years-old. We do not knowingly solicit data online from or market online to children under 13 years-old. If we knowingly receive a child’s personally identifiable information, we will immediately delete it from our system.  If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 years old and you believe we have received personal information from your child, please contact us at support@clickbooth.com.

 **LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

The Site may include links to other websites or mobile applications whose privacy practices may differ from ours. We are not responsible for any practices employed on third-party websites or applications, including the information and content contained on the website or application. If you submit information to a third-party website or application, your information is governed by the third party’s privacy policy. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website or application you visit, access or use.

 **ACCOUNTABILITY FOR ONWARD TRANSFERS**

To effectively serve the needs of our clients, Clickbooth may need to share that data with certain third parties or sub-processors. In such instances, Clickbooth will execute any needed contracts, clauses or addendums to ensure that any third-party agents that it engages to process personal data does so in a manner that is consistent with the Privacy Shield Principles. Clickbooth is potentially liable for onward transfers to third parties of personal data of EU individuals received pursuant to Privacy Shield.

 **EU-U.S. PRIVACY SHIELD FRAMEWORK**

Clickbooth.com, LLC complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States.  Clickbooth has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles.  If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Clickbooth commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information.  EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact Clickbooth at:

support@clickbooth.com

Clickbooth has further committed to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning data transferred from the EU.

 **JURISDICTION**

Clickbooth has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. Clickbooth states that if there is any conflict between the terms of our privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. Clickbooth is also subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC). To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view Clickbooth’s Privacy Shield certification, please visit [www.privacyshield.gov](http://www.privacyshield.gov/).

 **RECOURSE & ENFORCEMENT**

In instances where other redress possibilities have been exhausted under EU law, or where the complaint has not been resolved by any other means, EU end users may be entitled to invoke binding arbitration option before the Privacy Shield Panel. Clickbooth acknowledges that any final decision by the Privacy Shield Panel is a legally binding decision, enforceable in US courts.

 **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

Clickbooth has the discretion to update this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. In the event that we modify this Privacy Policy, we will communicate these changes to you by posting them on this Website and/or by notifying you via e-mail prior to the change becoming effective in the event of any substantive or material changes.  We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and to review our emails regarding substantive or material modifications.

 **YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

 **CONTACT INFORMATION**

We can be reached at the following address:

Clickbooth.com, LLC

Suite 114

5911 North Honore Avenue

Sarasota, FL 34243-2632

To contact us by phone, please call:

Phone: 941-483-4188

Toll Free: 866-TOP-OFFERS (866-867-6333)

To contact us by e-mail, please contact us at support@clickbooth.com.

EFFECTIVE DATE: May 10th, 2018
